export const maj72 = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: "Which note is the tonic (root) in the C Major scale?",
      choices: ["A", "C", "E", "G"],
      correctAnswer: "E",
      // clef: "bass",
      // timeSig: "4/4",
      keySig: "C",
      notes: "C4, D4, E4, F4, G4, A4, B4, C5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question: "In the C Major scale, what is the second-degree note?",
      choices: ["D", "F", "C", "A"],
      correctAnswer: "D",
      // clef: "bass",
      // timeSig: "4/4",
      keySig: "C",
      notes: "C4, D4, E4, F4, G4, A4, B4, C5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the relative minor key of C Major?",
      choices: ["E Minor", "C Minor", "A Minor", "G Minor"],
      correctAnswer: "A Minor",
      // clef: "bass",
      // timeSig: "4/4",
      keySig: "C",
      notes: "C4, D4, E4, F4, G4, A4, B4, C5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question: "Which note is raised by a half step in C Major?",
      choices: [
        "Between C and D",
        "Between F and G",
        "Between B and C",
        "Between A and B",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Between B and C",
      // clef: "bass",
      // timeSig: "4/4",
      keySig: "C",
      notes: "C4, D4, E4, F4, G4, A4, B4, C5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question:
        "How many sharps are in the C Major key signature of the treble clef?",
      choices: ["None", "One", "Two", "Three"],
      correctAnswer: "None",
      // clef: "bass",
      // timeSig: "4/4",
      keySig: "C",
      notes: "C4, D4, E4, F4, G4, A4, B4, C5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the subdominant chord in C Major?",
      choices: ["A Major", "E Minor", "F Minor", "F Major"],
      correctAnswer: "F Major",
      // clef: "bass",
      // timeSig: "4/4",
      keySig: "C",
      notes: "C4, D4, E4, F4, G4, A4, B4, C5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question: "What's the leading tone in the C Major scale?",
      choices: ["D", "C", "F", "B"],
      correctAnswer: "B",
      // clef: "bass",
      // timeSig: "4/4",
      keySig: "C",
      notes: "C4, D4, E4, F4, G4, A4, B4, C5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question: "Which note is the mediant in the C Major scale?",
      choices: ["A", "E", "Bb", "G#"],
      correctAnswer: "E",
      // clef: "bass",
      // timeSig: "4/4",
      keySig: "C",
      notes: "C4, D4, E4, F4, G4, A4, B4, C5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question:
        "What interval is formed between the first and fifth degrees of the C Major?",
      choices: [
        "Perfect Fifth",
        "Perfect Fourth",
        "Minor Sixth",
        "Major Fourth",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Perfect Fifth",
      // clef: "bass",
      // timeSig: "4/4",
      keySig: "C",
      notes: "C4, D4, E4, F4, G4, A4, B4, C5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the key signature of C Major?",
      choices: ["Three Sharps", "Two Flats", "No sharps or flats", "One Flat"],
      correctAnswer: "No sharps or flats",
      // clef: "bass",
      // timeSig: "4/4",
      keySig: "C",
      notes: "C4, D4, E4, F4, G4, A4, B4, C5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
  ],
};

export const min72 = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: "What's the relative major key of C Minor?",
      choices: ["C Major", "D-Flat Minor", "E-Flat Major", "F Major"],
      correctAnswer: "E-flat Major",
      // clef: "bass",
      // timeSig: "4/4",
      keySig: "Cm",
      notes: "C4, D4, E4, F4, G4, A4, B4, C5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question: "In the C Natural Minor scale, what is the third note?",
      choices: ["C", "E-flat", "G", "B-flat"],
      correctAnswer: "E-flat",
      // clef: "bass",
      // timeSig: "4/4",
      keySig: "Cm",
      notes: "C4, D4, E4, F4, G4, A4, B4, C5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following intervals represents the distance between the root and the fifth in a C Minor chord?",
      choices: ["Minor 3rd", "Perfect 4th", "Major 5th", "Minor 6th"],
      correctAnswer: "Major 5th",
      // clef: "bass",
      // timeSig: "4/4",
      keySig: "Cm",
      notes: "C4, D4, E4, F4, G4, A4, B4, C5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Harmonic minor scale in C Minor is distinguished by the raised. . .",
      choices: ["3rd", "6th", "7th", "6th and 7th"],
      correctAnswer: "6th and 7th",
      // clef: "bass",
      // timeSig: "4/4",
      keySig: "Cm",
      notes: "C4, D4, E4, F4, G4, A4, B4, C5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the key signature of C Minor?",
      choices: [
        "Three flats",
        "No sharps or flats",
        "Three sharps",
        "One flat",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Three flats",
      // clef: "bass",
      // timeSig: "4/4",
      keySig: "Cm",
      notes: "C4, D4, E4, F4, G4, A4, B4, C5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the dominant seventh chord in C Minor?",
      choices: ["C", "D", "G", "Bb"],
      correctAnswer: "G",
      // clef: "bass",
      // timeSig: "4/4",
      keySig: "Cm",
      notes: "C4, D4, E4, F4, G4, A4, B4, C5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the parallel major key of C Minor?",
      choices: ["C Major", "D Major", "E-flat Major", "F Major"],
      correctAnswer: "C Major",
      // clef: "bass",
      // timeSig: "4/4",
      keySig: "Cm",
      notes: "C4, D4, E4, F4, G4, A4, B4, C5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question: "In C Minor, what is the leading tone?",
      choices: ["B-flat", "B", "A", "G"],
      correctAnswer: "B",
      // clef: "bass",
      // timeSig: "4/4",
      keySig: "Cm",
      notes: "C4, D4, E4, F4, G4, A4, B4, C5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following chords is built on the fifth degree of the C Natural Minor scale?",
      choices: ["C Minor", "F Minor", "G Minor", "D Minor"],
      correctAnswer: "G Minor",
      // clef: "bass",
      // timeSig: "4/4",
      keySig: "Cm",
      notes: "C4, D4, E4, F4, G4, A4, B4, C5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question: "In C Minor, what is the submediant?",
      choices: ["A-Flat", "A", "G", "F"],
      correctAnswer: "A-Flat",
      // clef: "bass",
      // timeSig: "4/4",
      keySig: "Cm",
      notes: "C4, D4, E4, F4, G4, A4, B4, C5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
  ],
};

export const maj74 = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: "What is the relative minor key of D Major?",
      choices: ["D Minor", "E Minor", "A Minor", "B Minor"],
      correctAnswer: "B Minor",
      keySig: "D",
      notes: "D4, E4, F#4, G4, A4, B4, C#5, D5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following intervals represents the distance between the root and the fifth in a D Major chord?",
      choices: ["Minor 3rd", "Perfect 4th", "Major 5th", "Minor 6th"],
      correctAnswer: "Major 5th",
      keySig: "D",
      notes: "D4, E4, F#4, G4, A4, B4, C#5, D5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question: "In the D Major scale, what is the third note?",
      choices: ["D", "F#", "A", "C#"],
      correctAnswer: "F#",
      keySig: "D",
      notes: "D4, E4, F#4, G4, A4, B4, C#5, D5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which triad is formed on the seventh degree of the D Major scale?",
      choices: ["Major", "Minor", "Diminished", "Augmented"],
      correctAnswer: "Diminished",
      keySig: "D",
      notes: "D4, E4, F#4, G4, A4, B4, C#5, D5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the parallel minor key of D Major?",
      choices: ["D Minor", "E Minor", "A Minor", "B Minor"],
      correctAnswer: "D Minor",
      keySig: "D",
      notes: "D4, E4, F#4, G4, A4, B4, C#5, D5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question: "The tonic triad in D Major consists of the notes:",
      choices: ["D, F#, A", "E, G, B", "F#, A, C#", "G, B, D"],
      correctAnswer: "D, F#, A",
      keySig: "D",
      notes: "D4, E4, F#4, G4, A4, B4, C#5, D5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the quality of the triad built on the sixth degree of the D Major scale?",
      choices: ["Major", "Minor", "Diminished", "Augmented"],
      correctAnswer: "Minor",
      keySig: "D",
      notes: "D4, E4, F#4, G4, A4, B4, C#5, D5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question: "In D Major, what is the submediant?",
      choices: ["B", "G", "A", "F#"],
      correctAnswer: "B",
      keySig: "D",
      notes: "D4, E4, F#4, G4, A4, B4, C#5, D5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question:
        "The subdominant chord in D Major is built on which degree of the scale?",
      choices: ["1st", "2nd", "3rd", "4th"],
      correctAnswer: "4th",
      keySig: "D",
      notes: "D4, E4, F#4, G4, A4, B4, C#5, D5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the key signature of the relative minor key of D Major?",
      choices: [
        "No sharps or flats",
        "Three flats",
        "Three sharps",
        "One flat",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "One sharp",
      keySig: "D",
      notes: "D4, E4, F#4, G4, A4, B4, C#5, D5",
      selectedAnswer: "",
    },
  ],
};
